quoners.com 2017-06-06

# Quoners Privacy Policy

The user www.quoners.com WebSite (hereinafter sometimes Company) may provide certain personal data. According to the provisions of Law 15/1999 of December 13, Protection of Personal Data and its implementing regulations, approved by Royal Decree 1720/2007 of December 21, we inform you that the data personal obtained as a result of the collection through forms, will be added to the file "Users" www.quoners.com ownership

The User guarantees that the personal data provided to the Company are true and correct, and responsible for communicating any changes in them.

Users have and may exercise their rights of access, cancellation, rectification and opposition, and the right, if they so request in writing, to be informed of assignments made thereof.

## Purposes

The Organic Law of Protection of Personal Data applies regardless of the number of records stored, or an automated or not the files, ie, it applies to any organized set of personal data, whatever the manner or method of its creation, storage, organization, processing and access.

The collection and processing of personal data of any of the forms of www.quoners.com WebSite, aims sending information about our services, access to and usability of the same, the resolution of any questions exposed by the user and the application on-line by the same of any products and / or services offered.

## Transfer

www.quoners.com not currently performs assignments of personal data of the User to third.

However, the user, to provide their data, given their free, unequivocal, specific and informed to www.quoners.com, can treat them in accordance with the purposes described in paragraphs "Disclaimer" and "Policy Privacy "of the website, as well as giving it and transmit it to other national and international organizations that are part of the same group and / or companies associated with it, for the sole purpose of enabling them to deal with their business information to provide about their products or services. www.quoners.com, is committed to protecting the personal data collected, using them only for specified purposes and not for other purposes.

## Exercise of rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition

The User can send messages and exercise their rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition to the processing of personal data by regular mail addressed to:

www.quoners.com Ref. LOPD quoners @ quoners .com

In accordance with Instruction 1/1998, of 19 January, the Data Protection Agency, to exercise those rights is necessary for the user practicing to prove your identity www.quoners.com by sending a photocopy of national Identity Card or any other legally valid identification document.

In accordance with applicable law in this area, the concept of treatment refers to all operations and technical procedures of an automated or not, enabling the collection, recording, storage, processing, modification, blocking and cancellation, as well as assignments of data resulting from communications, consultations, interconnections and transfers.

www.quoners.com, informs them that they may use your email address to send electronic communications, continue to apply the provisions of Law 32/2003, of 3 November, General Telecommunications, referring to similar services that you access through the web Site.

www.quoners.com, provides users with a mechanism, simple and free, to withdraw the consent given for the purpose of sending electronic communications, in full compliance with European and national legislation on the matter referred.

## Disclaimer Clause

www.quoners.com, assumes no responsibility for the information provided and contained in this site.

## Security Measures

The Company has adopted the levels and security measures to protect personal data installed on their systems and files the necessary technical measures to guarantee the confidentiality of the data and avoid loss, alteration and access.

Nevertheless, the user should be aware that Internet security measures are not impregnable.

## What protects the user's personal data?

The information contained in this website is covered by a system of personal data protection and privacy policy email.

Electronic services - For each specific e-service offering www.quoners.com, a controller (manager) determines the purposes and means of the processing of personal data obtained and ensures that the service fits the protection policy data.

The establishment of a link, link exchange, not in any way imply the existence of relations between managers www.quoners.com, and the owner of the web site with which it is established, nor the acceptance and approval of its contents or services.

Www.quoners.com managers, exclude all liability on any sites linked to this site and can not control and do not control that appear including Internet sites whose contents may be unlawful, illegal, contrary to morality or decency or inappropriate. You therefore should exercise caution in evaluating and using the information, content and services available on the linked sites.

Www.quoners.com managers, also exclude all liability for posts, reviews, news and information posted by users, third parties and the same shall be liable to users or others who come.

Email - will record the personal information necessary to respond to email. If you have any questions about the processing of their messages or data contained therein, please include it in the messages you send us.

## Acceptance and Consent

Users acknowledge having been informed of the conditions of protection of personal data, accepting and consenting to the processing of the same by the Company, in the manner and for the purposes stated in this Policy for the Protection of Personal Data.

## Law and Jurisdiction

In general, the relationship between the Company and the Users of its telematic services on the Web, are subject to Spanish law.

All disputes, controversies or circumstances arising from the special and general conditions are subject to the courts of the City and Villa de Madrid, the parties expressly waive any other jurisdiction that may correspond.

There are many different ways you can use our services - to search for and share information, to communicate with other people or to create new content. When you share information with us, for example by creating a Quoners.com Account, we can make those services even better to help you connect with people or to make sharing with others quicker and easier. As you use our services, we want you to be clear how we´re using information and the ways in which you can protect your privacy.

Our Privacy Policy explains:

  * What information we collect and why we collect it.
  * How we use that information.
  * The choices we offer, including how to access and update information.

We´ve tried to keep it as simple as possible, but if you´re not familiar with terms like cookies, IP addresses, pixel tags and browsers, then read about these key terms first. Your privacy matters to **Quoners.com** so whether you are new to **Quoners.com** or a long-time user, please do take the time to get to know our practices - and if you have any questions contact us.

## Information we collect

We collect information to provide better services to all of our users - from figuring out basic stuff like which language you speak, to more complex things like which ads you´ll find most useful or the people who matter most to you online.

We collect information in two ways:

  * **Information you give us**. For example, many of our services require you to sign up for a **Quoners.com Account**. When you do, we´ll ask for personal information, like your name, email address or telephone number. If you want to take full advantage of the sharing features we offer, we might also ask you to create a publicly visible **Quoners.com Profile** , which may include your name and photo.
  * **Information we get from your use of our services**. We may collect information about the services that you use and how you use them, like when you view and interact with our ads and content. This information includes:
    * **Device information**  
We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information including phone number). **Quoners.com** may associate your device identifiers or phone number with your **Quoners.com Account**.
    * **Log information**  
When you use our services or view content provided by Quoners.com, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. This may include:
      * details of how you used our service, such as your search queries.
      * Internet protocol address.
      * device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL.
      * cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your **Quoners.com Account**.
  * **Location information**  
When you use a **location-enabled Quoners.com service** , we may collect and process information about your actual location, like GPS signals sent by a mobile device.
  * **Local storage**  
We may collect and store information (including personal information) locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches.
  * **Cookies and anonymous identifiers**  
We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit a **Quoners.com service** , and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device. We also use cookies and anonymous identifiers when you interact with services we offer to our partners, such as advertising services or **Quoners.com** features that may appear on other sites.

## How we use information we collect

We use the information we collect from all of our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new ones, and to protect **Quoners.com** and our users. We also use this information to offer you tailored content - like giving you more relevant search results and ads.

When you contact Quoners.com, we may keep a record of your communication to help solve any issues you might be facing. We may use your email address to inform you about our services, such as letting you know about upcoming changes or improvements.

We use information collected from cookies and other technologies, like pixel tags, to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our services. For example, by saving your language preferences, we´ll be able to have our services appear in the language you prefer.

We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are set out in this Privacy Policy.

Quoners.com processes personal information on our servers in many countries around the world. We may process your personal information on a server located outside the country where you live.

## Transparency and choice

People have different privacy concerns. Our goal is to be clear about what information we collect, so that you can make meaningful choices about how it is used. For example, you can:

  * Use our editor to see and adjust how your **Quoners.com Profile** appears to particular individuals.
  * Control who you share information with.
  * Take information out of many of our services.

You may also set your browser to block all cookies, including cookies associated with our services, or to indicate when a cookie is being set by us. However, it´s important to remember that many of our services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. For example, we may not remember your language preferences.

## Information you share

Many of our services let you share information with others. Remember that when you share information publicly, it may be indexable by search engines, including **Quoners.com**. Our services provide you with different options on sharing and removing your content.

## Accessing and updating your personal information

Whenever you use our services, we aim to provide you with access to your personal information. If that information is wrong, we strive to give you ways to update it quickly or to delete it - unless we have to keep that information for legitimate business or legal purposes. When updating your personal information, we may ask you to verify your identity before we can act on your request.

Where we can provide information access and correction, we will do so for free, except where it would require a disproportionate effort. We aim to maintain our services in a manner that protects information from accidental or malicious destruction. Because of this, after you delete information from our services, we may not immediately delete residual copies from our active servers and may not remove information from our backup systems.

## Information we share

We do not share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of **Quoners.com** unless one of the following circumstances apply:

  * **With your consent**  
We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of **Quoners.com** when we have your consent to do so. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.
  * **For external processing**  
We provide personal information to our affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * **For legal reasons**  
We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of **Quoners.com** if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:
    * meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
    * enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.
    * detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
    * protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Quoners.com, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

We may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information publicly and with our partners - like publishers, advertisers or connected sites. For example, we may share information publicly to show trends about the general use of our services.

## Information security

We work hard to protect **Quoners.com** and our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. In particular:

  * We review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to systems.
  * We restrict access to personal information to **Quoners.com employees** , contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

## Application

Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by **Quoners.com**.

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you in search results, sites that may include **Quoners.com services** , or other sites linked from our services. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise our services, and who may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads.

## Enforcement

We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy.

## Changes

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes). We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

### KEY TERMS

#### Personal information

This is information which you provide to us which personally identifies you, such as your name, email address or billing information, or other data which can be reasonably linked to such information by Quoners.com.

#### Quoners.com Account

You may access some of our services by signing up for a **Quoners.com Account** and providing us with some personal information (typically your name, email address and a password). This account information will be used to authenticate you when you access **Quoners.com** services and protect your account from unauthorized access by others. You can edit or terminate your account at any time through your **Quoners.com Account** settings.

#### Cookie

A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies.

#### Anonymous identifier

An anonymous identifier is a random string of characters that is used for the same purposes as a cookie on platforms, including certain mobile devices, where cookie technology is not available.

#### IP address

Every computer connected to the Internet is assigned a unique number known as an Internet protocol (IP) address. Since these numbers are usually assigned in country-based blocks, an IP address can often be used to identify the country from which a computer is connecting to the Internet.

#### Server logs

Like most websites, our servers automatically record the page requests made when you visit our sites. These "server logs" typically include your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

Here is an example of a typical log entry where the search is for "cars", followed by a breakdown of its parts:

`123.45.67.89 - 25/Mar/2003 10:15:32 - http://www.Quoners.com/search?qcars - Firefox 1.0.7; Windows NT 5.1 - 740674ce2123e969`

  * `133.45.67.69`is the Internet Protocol address assigned to the user by the user´s ISP; depending on the user´s service, a different address may be assigned to the user by their service provider each time they connect to the Internet;
  * `25/Mar/2009 10:15:32`is the date and time of the query;
  * `http://www.Quoners.com/search?q=law`is the requested URL, including the search query;
  * `Firefox 1.0.6; Windows NT 5.1`is the browser and operating system being used; and
  * `7402345ddr2123a969`is the unique cookie ID assigned to this particular computer the first time it visited Quoners.com. (Cookies can be deleted by users. If the user has deleted the cookie from the computer since the last time s/he visited Quoners.com, then it will be the unique cookie ID assigned to the user the next time s/he visits **Quoners.com** from that particular computer).

#### Sensitive personal information

This is a particular category of personal information relating to confidential medical facts, racial or ethnic origins, political or religious beliefs or sexuality.

#### Non-personally identifiable information

This is information that is recorded about users so that it no longer reflects or references an individually identifiable user.

#### Pixel tag

A pixel tag is a type of technology placed on a website or within the body of an email for the purpose of tracking activity on websites, or when emails are opened or accessed, and is often used in combination with cookies.
